A Finding Aid to the Arnold Rönnebeck and Louise Emerson Rönnebeck Papers, 1884-2002, in the Archives of American Art AAA.ronnarno
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Materials, 1884-1976; Series 7; 2.6 Linear feet Box 2-6
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Reliefs and Busts (Omaha, NE), scanned with Box 3, Folder 25, circa 1925-1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Busts, Men, scanned with Box 3, Folder 26, circa 1915-1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculptures, scanned with Box 3, Folders 38, 43, circa 1915-1955 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Frescoes and Murals, scanned with Box 4, Folders 3, 10, 12, circa 1925-1955 (Box 6, Folder 3)